

Applicant for:

Developer Engineer (PHP or C# or Java)

Starboard Asia Co.,ltd. 12 June 2018

CHOYON

Main interests: JavaScript, PHP

What skills, work projects or achievements make you a strong candidate for this position?

I've 6+ years of experience on Web Application development with extensive knowledge about OOP, RDMS, MVC, AWS, RESTFull API, Version Controll (git). Laravel, Vue JS, Symfony, Angular JS, WordPress are my favorite.



BHATTACHARJEE

HAPPINESS ENGINEER

KEYS

- Team Player
- Quick Learner
- Hard Worker
- Pro Active
- Perfectionist

CONTACT



contact.choyon@gmail.com

www.choyon.net



WORK EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

12/2010 - 10/2013 **FULL TIME**

SOFTWARE ARCHITECT

12/2013 - 09/2014 PART TIME REMOTE

PROJECT LEAD

05/2016 - 09/2017 PART TIME REMOTE

TEAM LEAD

11/2014 -**FULL TIME**

W 3 E N G I N E E R S

- Design and Develop PHP/WordPress based custom application for different clients.
- Scrapping, Documentation, Content writing.

BOONMFDIA

- Property Listing using CREA and Custom API
- Application architecture, ERD, System Analysis, Database Management

BUCKETLIST. CITY

• Application architecture, System Analysis, Database Management, Quality Assurance.

SYSTWAY

• Requirement Analysis, Problem Solving, Manage and plan for different projects, Divide tasks within team members, Client Communication,



EDUCATION



BSC. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE & ENGINEERING

KHULNA UNIVERSITY. KHULNA-9100 BANGLADESH



SKILLS

Manage/Planning PHP/MySQL/Laravel/WordPress CI/Symfony 2/Yii JS/jQuery/Vue Js/Angular Js API/MVC/OOP/RDMS/git

